Previously on Space Brothers...
なんば　むった
＜これまでの宇宙兄弟＞
＜あのシャロンが
エーエルエス
ＡＬＳと診断された｡➡
Sharon was diagnosed with ALS.
In a few months, she will no longer be able to play the piano anymore.
あと数ヶ月で 大好きなピアノも
弾けなくなってしまう＞
俺が誰より先に選ばれて➡
I plan to be the first one chosen to go to the moon and build your telescope.
月で望遠鏡を建てる予定だよ｡
＜シャロンが
日本へ帰国した一方…＞
After Sharon returned to Japan...
ワシに ついてこられるなら➡
If you can keep up with me,
you'll progress 1.5 times faster than everyone else.
他の奴の１.５倍早く
仕上げてやるぞ｡
＜私は宇宙飛行士になるために
欠かせない➡
Flight training in a T-38 jet is the next step to becoming an astronaut.
ジェット練習機 Ｔ－３８の
そうじゅう
操縦訓練へ＞
(ﾃﾞﾆｰﾙ)飛行前のチェック作業は
気を抜くな ムッタ｡
When checking an aircraft, never cut corners.
事故った時 整備士に
責任を押し付けるのは➡
The worst thing a pilot can do is crash and get his maintenance crew in trouble.
パイロットの恥っちゅうもんだ｡
今のは心のノートに
メモっとけ｡
Put that in the notebook in your heart.
However, my training wasn't going too well.
＜しかし 決して訓練は
順調とはいえない＞
It's just obvious that the more you put in your bag
The heavier it gets
The harder I work, the closer I get to my goal
But I'm just not getting there fast enough
I gaze at the night sky but it doesn't calm me down
Now that you've heard how loud my heart's beating
Let's take a trip outside
My starvation knows no bounds under this sea of stars
In this planetarium of dreams and reality
I'm currently updating the canvas of my dreams
With a glittering universe and a blue earth
My starvation knows no bounds under this sea of stars
In this planetarium of facades and honesty
I'm currently conversing with the canvas of my dreams
On this orbit of fate
With a fire in my belly
#67 Deneil-ized
[ﾗｼﾞｵ](ＤＪ)聴くと元気になる
モーニングレディオ！➡
It's the morning show that gets you going!
Time for some Q&A, yeah!
Ｑ＆Ａのコーナー イエ～イ！
[ﾗｼﾞｵ](ＤＪ)
ロスにお住まいのカールくん
７歳からの質問！➡
Let's start with a question from seven-year-old Carl, out in LA.
この前 家族旅行で
日本へ行った時➡
"I went to Japan on a family vacation,
and there was salt outside the restaurant's entrance.
お店の前に
塩が飾ってありました｡➡
Why do the Japanese put salt outside?"
どうして日本人は
塩を入り口に置くんですか？
[ﾗｼﾞｵ](ＤＪ)なるほど～いい質問だね
カールくん それはね…➡
Ah, that's an excellent question, Carl.
The answer is...
砂糖だと
アリが寄ってくるからだよ！
Because sugar would attract ants!
What are you doing?
ひびと
(南波日々人)何してんの それ？
I'm practicing how it feels to fly a T-38
Ｔ－３８で背面飛行する時のね
動きの訓練だよ｡
while inverted.
Oh, you're already flying inverted?
へえ～！
もう背面飛行なんてやってんの！
フッフッフッフ 余裕でな｡
It was a breeze.
《本当はまだ…
景色を見る余裕すらない…➡
Honestly, I don't even have the time to look out the window.
日々人は楽勝で
見れるんだろうな…》
Hibito probably had plenty of time to enjoy it...
[TV]モドナルドに でっかい奴が
やって来た！➡
There's a new giant in town at MoDonald...
Bam!
ギャオー!!
トリプルバーガー新登場！
It's the new Triple Burger.
How are we supposed to eat it?!
[TV]どうやって食べたら
いいんだ～!?
[TV]オー マイ ゴッド！
Oh my god!
Can anyone defeat the MoDonald Triple Burger?
[TV]誰かコイツを倒してくれ！
モドナルド トリプルバーガー！
ごっそ～さん｡あ そうだ｡
I'm stuffed.
Oh, right...
俺 来月から日本に一時帰国だよ｡
Next month, I'm returning to Japan for a while.
ジャクサ
デブリーフィング
ＪＡＸＡで事後報告会議とか
講演会とか｡
JAXA wants to have me lecture and to debrief me.
あと…シャロンのとこにも
顔出すよ｡
And then, I'll go see Sharon.
Y-Yeah, I appreciate it.
お…おう 頼んだ｡
さて 俺も体力戻ってきたことだし
今日からチャリで行くわ｡お先｡
Well, I've recovered most of my strength...
I think I'll take my bike today.
I'm off...
あ…そう｡あっ｡
Ah, okay.
Wow! It's so shiny!
スゲー！
ピッカピカになってる～！
ムッちゃん 磨いてくれたんだ！
ありがとう｡
You polished it for me, Mu!
Thanks...
No big deal.
ふふん｡
No thanks necessary.
礼なんか いいんだよ～｡
行ってきま～す｡
See ya!
Huh?
あ～！ちっ…｡
Bah!
He didn't even notice?
あれに気付かんとは…相変わらず
ネジが１本 足りない奴だ｡
That kid still has a screw loose in his head.
あ…おっとぉ｡
Whoa...
へっへへへ…｡
ピッカピカァ～！
It's so shiny!
Flight Max... Mr. Nanba.
マックス号 ミスターナンバ！
こちら管制塔｡
This is Air Traffic Control.
飛行ルートが ずれてるぞ｡
機首方位130度へ右旋回｡➡
You've left your flight path.
Turn your nose right, 130 degrees,
高度33000フィートへ
上昇してくれ｡
and ascend to an altitude of 33,000 feet.
りょ…了解！
R-Roger that!
Hey, what should we have for lunch, Mutta?
なあ 昼メシ何食うよ ムッタ？
ちょっと黙ってて！
Can't you shut up?!
え～と 風向は２４０
風速は１０ノットか｡
Uh, wind direction is 240 degrees, wind speed is 10 knots,
and I'm currently at flight level 200...
今がフライトレベル･
トゥーゼロセロで…｡
すべ
(ﾃﾞﾆｰﾙ)右に滑ってるぞ ムッタ｡
えっ!?あ しまった！
You're angling right, Mutta!
Eh?! Crap!
Damn, this isn't working out.
《ちくしょ～！
全然うまくいかね～な！➡
Too much to do... I'm losing control!
あ～忙しいぜ！
テンパってきた！》
＜宇宙飛行士に必要とされる
マルチタスクの技量｡➡
An astronaut must be able to multitask.
In other words, you must be able to accomplish multiple tasks within a limited time.
すなわち 時間内に多くの仕事を
しゅんぱつ
正確にこなす瞬発力｡➡
このＴ－３８飛行訓練は
きた
まさに その瞬発力を鍛えるのに➡
Training in the T-38 is a perfect way to develop multitasking skills, but...
うってつけ
というわけなのだが…＞
景気付けに踊ろうぜ ムッタ！
Let's do some dancing, Mutta!
え!?ちょっと待て！今 それどころ
じゃないだろ ヤンじい！
Wait... Hold on!
I'm busy right now, Mr. Young!
I'm hitting the override.
(ﾃﾞﾆｰﾙ)オーバーライドする｡
Wait... S-Stop!
ちょっと…や やめて！
《いかんせん 邪魔が入りまくる》
...But I keep getting interrupted.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
ウハハハ！ムッタ 操縦交代だ｡
お前やれ！
Mutta, I'm giving you control.
Take over.
Eh? Now?
えっ!?ここで!?
いよ～！
And this guy won't stop talking.
《そして この男 喋りまくる》
This is what a father said to the son who was always playing games and never studied...
ゲームばっかして勉強しない
息子に父親は言いました｡➡
リンカーンは お前と同じ年の頃➡
"When Lincoln was your age, he read by the light from a stove."
だんろ
あか
暖炉の灯りで
本を読んでいたんだぞ｡
Oh, yeah...
But the son had a response for him.
(ﾃﾞﾆｰﾙ)そう言われて息子は父親に
こう言い返しました｡➡
Can you guess what it was?
さて…何と言った？
だから！それどころじゃね～んだ
こっちは！
Seriously...
I really am busy right now!
この速度でＯＫだよな ヤンじい？
Is my speed okay, Mr. Young?
(ﾃﾞﾆｰﾙ)はい 時間切れ｡
E-Eh?
You're out of time!
息子は父親に
こう言い返しました｡➡
Here's what the son had to say...
リンカーンは父さんと同じ年の頃
アメリカ大統領だったけどね｡➡
"When Lincoln was your age, he was President of the United States of America!"
Yo, Mutta... You looked exhausted.
(ﾄﾆｰ)よう ムッタ｡
ずいぶん お疲れだな｡
(ﾄﾆｰ)楽しいもんじゃないか
飛行訓練なんて｡➡
Flight training is a lot of fun.
Stop moping around.
そう落ち込むなよ｡
Right.
《あの人たちは なんで
あんなに余裕なんだ？》
Why are they so relaxed?
《マルチタスクが
うまくいってんのかな…➡
Do they already have multitasking down?
こんなに難しいのに…》
But it's so hard.
はあく
《｢多くの情報を瞬時に把握し
飲み込まなければ｣➡
As soon as I had an idea about how I should swallow all the information around me,
という思考が
どう転がったか 途中➡
I suddenly had the image of a huge hamburger that was way too big for my mouth.
くち
ひら
｢こんなに口 開かね～よ｣と
ツッコミたくなるような➡
具材 積み過ぎのハンバーガーが
頭をよぎったりする始末…》
かっ あっ｡よっ！
In other words, I can't focus.
《ようするに…集中できていない
ということになるな 俺は》
Hey, Mutta...
お～い ムッタ｡
Huh?
Break time.
休憩だ 屋上でのんびりしよ～ぜ｡
あい…｡
Let's kick back on the roof.
Okay.
I don't get it.
《おっかしいな…➡
I always thought I was good at multitasking...
俺は元々 こういうの
得意だと思ってだんだけどな…》
There we go.
よっこいせ｡ふう～｡
いや～最高だな ハンモックは｡
Yeah, I love hammocks.
ちょっと ゆすってくれや ムッタ｡
あとで かわってやるからよ｡
Could you rock me for a bit, Mutta?
We can trade places later.
《ちっ 地面スレスレじゃね～か》
It's almost touching the ground.
おお いいぞ｡
Yeah, that's good...
Didn't you say you'd help me progress 1.5 times faster, Mr. Young?
《俺を１.５倍で仕上げて
くれるんじゃなかったのかよ➡
ヤンじい｡なんか他のメンバーより
遅れてる気がするぞ…》
It feels like I'm falling behind everyone.
Wait.
《いや…俺ができね～ことを➡
I shouldn't blame this old man for my own shortcomings.
この じいさんのせいにすんのも
やぼな話だよな》
Listen to me, Mutta...
(ﾃﾞﾆｰﾙ)いいか ムッタ｡
心のノートにメモっとけ｡
Put this in the notebook in your heart.
一流のパイロットは
飛行機を飛ばしながら➡
A top pilot can tell witty jokes while flying.
気の利いたジョークも飛ばせる｡
ハハハハッ わかるな｡
ワシが いかに一流だったか｡
Now do you understand how good I am?
(ﾃﾞﾆｰﾙ)あとな 一流のパイロットは
いつでもどこでも➡
One more thing...
A top pilot can do acrobatics at any time, in any place.
アクロバットで楽しめる｡➡
If you can draw a heart in the sky, you're qualified.
空にハートマークでも描けりゃ
ひとまず一人前だ｡
ヤンじいは そう
一流一流って言うけどさ｡
You keep talking about top pilots, Mr. Young.
俺は宇宙飛行士になろうと
しているわけで➡
But I'm trying to become an astronaut.
一流のパイロットにまでなる
必要はないと思うんだよな｡
I don't think I need to be a top pilot...
Or draw hearts in the sky.
空にハート描いたりとか｡
んなことは わかってるぜ！
I know that.
Huh?
ワシはな ムッタ…｡
You see, Mutta...
I want you to become a top astronaut.
お前に一流の宇宙飛行士に
なってもらいたいと思ってるんだ｡
しかしワシには
一流の宇宙飛行士になる➡
But I don't know what it takes to become a top astronaut,
方法などわからんし
教え方も知らん｡➡
so I don't know what to teach you.
However...
だが…一流のパイロットになる
方法なら教えられる｡
I know what to teach you
to make you a top pilot.
やれるとこまでやって
何か見つけろよ ムッタ｡➡
Do what you can until you learn what you need, Mutta.
どうせやるなら
その道の一流を目指そうぜ｡
If you're going to try something, you may as well aim for the top.
なあ ヤンじい｡ハートが描けたら
一人前なんだな｡
Hey, Mr. Young...
If I draw a heart, I'm qualified, right?
Yeah, that's right.
ああ そうだ｡しかも いいことは
それだけじゃない！➡
And that's not all.
ひろう
意中の女にでも披露してみろ｡➡
If you ensure your sweetheart is watching,
かなりの確率でイチコロだぞ｡
you stand a good chance of getting your girl.
ワシは そうやって
カミさんを射止めた｡
That's how I won my wife.
Oh... Really?
な なるほど｡
背面飛行で行くぞ ムッタ！
Let's flip her upside-down, Mutta.
Okay.
ＯＫ！
(ﾃﾞﾆｰﾙ)ノーズを下げるな！
Keep your nose straight.
Hey, Mr. Young?
なあ ヤンじい｡この飛行訓練が
規定の240時間を終了してさ➡
Once I log the 240 required hours of flight training
俺が宇宙飛行士に
認定された後も➡
and I become an official astronaut...
休みの日とか また
ここに来るから➡
I'll drop by when I have time off, so teach me a move or two.
わざ
なんか 技を教えてくれよ｡
ハハハ！ずいぶん気の早い話だが
いい心構えだ！
You're thinking a little far ahead,
but that's more like it!
しかし…悪いがムッタ｡
その約束はできん｡
Unfortunately, I can't promise you anything.
Huh?
(ﾃﾞﾆｰﾙ)今回 担当する教え子が➡
Once the student I'm currently assigned to becomes an official astronaut,
宇宙飛行士に認定されたら
ワシは引退すると決めとった｡
I'm going to retire...
You're my last student, Mutta.
お前が最後の生徒だ ムッタ｡
Huh?!
＜なぜだか この瞬間から私は➡
For some reason, that was the moment
せんめい
窓の外の景色を鮮明に
見れるようになった＞
I became able to see the view outside.
＜上を見れば
そこには地球があり➡
I look up to see Earth,
下の方には
宇宙が広がっていた＞
and look down to see the expanse of space.
お～い ヤンじい～｡
Hey, Mr. Young?
そろそろ時間だよ～｡
どこ行った？
It's almost time!
Where'd you go?
ねえ ヤンじい 知らない？
Hey, have you seen Mr. Young?
(男)あ～屋上じゃねえか？
ハンモックだろ｡
Oh, he's probably on the roof.
Using the hammock.
またか！飛ばし屋のくせに
のんびり屋め｡
Again?
Flyboys aren't supposed to be laid-back.
Hmm?
俺の仕事はラストの一発勝負｡➡
My job is to deliver one last home run.
ドンケツに花開くまでは
日の目なんて見ることはねえ｡➡
It isn't over until you're on the ground, under the sun.
だが俺のパラシュートが
バッと開いた直後から➡
But the second my parachute opens,
それまでの しょっぱい酒がウソの
ようにうまく感じるようになる｡➡
my liquor starts tasting good again.
そして まあ あれだ｡
これを言うために➡
And ultimately, all the work I invest is so I can say these words.
今まで やってきたような
もんだからな｡
(ピコ)ウホン！心おきなく
言わせてもらうぜ｡
I'm gonna enjoy this...
Welcome home!
おかえり 諸君｡
(日々人･ﾘﾝﾀﾞ･ﾀﾞﾐｱﾝ)ただいま～！
Good to be back!
(ピコ)ウハハ いや～長かったぜ
ここまで｡
Yeah, it took a long time to get here.
悪いね ピコ｡こんな昼間にしか
みんな時間 合わなくて｡
Sorry, Pico.
This was the only time everyone could get together.
かまやしねえよ｡報告会議だの
なんだので忙しいんだろ？
It's fine...
You're probably busy with press conferences and all that stuff.
それに俺は いつだって
飲めるようにできてる｡
Besides, I'm always ready to get drunk.
あ～うめえな～｡
Delicious!
あっそういや ムッタのヤローは
今 何してんだ？
Oh, what's Mutta doing now?
主には飛行訓練だよ｡
デニールに教わってる｡
He's in flight training.
His instructor is Deneil.
Huh? That Deneil?
え？デニールってあのデニールか｡
しゅうしょうさま
ハハハ！ご愁傷様だな｡
I feel sorry for him...
まあ 最初の頃はムッちゃんも
しばらく顔色 悪かったけどね｡
Well, Mu didn't look so good at first.
最近は すげ～楽しそうに
やってるよ｡
But now, he's having lots of fun.
俺も そうだったけど｡
It was the same way for me.
デニール化してからが楽しいんだ｡
(ピコ)デニール化？
It's more fun once you're Deneil-ized.
Deneil-ized?
いじ
高度12000フィート維持｡➡
Maintain altitude at 12,000 feet.
せんかい
左旋回で機首を３０度の方向へ｡
Turn to the left 30 degrees.
了解！
(ﾃﾞﾆｰﾙ)お～い ムッタ➡
Roger that.
Hey, Mutta...
次のアメリカンジョーク問題
いくぞ！
Ready for the next question in my American joke quiz?
先生は聞いた｡ワシントンが
桜の木を切ったことを➡
A teacher asked the following...
"When George Washington confessed to cutting down a cherry tree,
正直に話した時 彼の父親は
すぐに許しました｡➡
his father immediately forgave him.
なぜだか わかりますか？
Do you know why?"
その問いに生徒は こう答えた｡
さて何と答えた？
One of the students had the answer.
Can you guess what it was?
《風向２７０ 風速６ノット》
Wind at 270 degrees. Wind speed, 6 knots.
Sure.
そうだな～｡
《姿勢･高度速度 良し！》
Attitude, altitude, and speed are all good.
生徒は こう答えた｡➡
This is what the student said...
おの
｢きっとワシントンが まだ斧を
持っていたからです｣｡
"Because George Washington was still holding the axe!"
(ﾃﾞﾆｰﾙ)ウハハハ！正解！
調子いいな ムッタ｡
Correct!
You're on a roll, Mutta!
American Jokes
ハハハッ 今のアメジョは
頭のノートにメモってあったぜ！
I had that joke written down in the notebook in my head.
(ﾃﾞﾆｰﾙ)おお おお 言うように
なったじゃねぇか｡➡
Hey, you're getting pretty cocky...
空の上では とにかく すごい
しゃべるんだよ デニールは｡
Deneil talks so much when he's in the sky!
ハイな気分になるってのも
あるんだろうけど➡
Part of it is because he's feeling high,
たぶん あれは ほとんど
ワザとやってると見た｡
but I suspect he does it deliberately.
何のために？
ふか
訓練初期から やたらと負荷を➡
Why?
Deneil tends to overload his students right off the bat.
かけてくんのが
デニール流なんだよ｡
管制から指示を受けた
直後だろうと おかまいなしに➡
The second you finish receiving Air Traffic Control instructions,
どお～でもいい話題とか
クイズとか始めるんだ｡
he'll start talking about nothing or quizzing you.
フンッ そうやって
こうもく
頭の中の処理項目を➡
So he's giving you multiple things to think about, all at the same time?
どんどん追加していくわけか｡
ハッ いいやり方だ｡
俺は好きだぜ｡
That's a good method.
Consider me a fan.
ムッタがテンパってる姿が
目に浮かぶってもんだ｡
I can already see Mutta panicking.
わずら
でも その負荷が煩わしいから➡
But because of the initial burden, most request a different instructor.
みんな途中で教官を
変えてくれってなっちゃうのよ｡
俺も一度だけデニールと
マックス号に乗った事あるけど➡
I rode with Deneil in his Max once...
正直 死ぬかと思ったよ｡
I honestly thought I'd die.
《ヒビトは よくあれに
耐えられたもんだ》
I can't believe Hibito actually survived.
つっても しゃべることだけが
負荷じゃないんだ｡
And it isn't just his talking that takes attention.
デニール仕様に改造された
あつか
マックス号も扱いづらいし➡
After Deneil's customizations to Max, it's tougher to control,
デニールの重い体重のせいで
バランスとるのも かなり難しい｡
and Deneil's weight makes it harder to keep balanced.
他の教官と乗った時
初めて その事に気付くんだけど➡
I didn't realize that until I flew with another instructor.
デニールとしか乗ってない
ムッちゃんは まだ知らない｡
Since Mu's only flown with Deneil, he doesn't know that yet.
もうデニール化しちゃってる
頃かもね｡
I'd bet he's in the process of being Deneil-ized.
おい！なんだ こりゃ｡
Hey, what's going on?
ヒャー 驚いたぜ ムッタ｡
今のは よかった！
I'm impressed, Mutta...
That was great!
ハッハッハッ！こんなもんよ｡
Too easy.
んで 高度チェックと…｡
Then I check my altitude...
｢じゃあ 次だ ムッタ！答えろ！➡
Okay, Mutta, next question!
『ＮＡＳＡ』と『ﾏｲｹﾙ･ｼﾞｬｸｿﾝ』の
共通点は？｣｡
What do NASA and Michael Jackson have in common?
高度3000フィート 減速下降中｡
着陸態勢に入る｡
Current altitude is 3,000 feet.
Descend while decelerating.
Prepare for landing.
Eh, what's that?
｢え～何だろ｡
ＮＡＳＡとマイケル？➡
NASA and Michael?
実は どっちも宇宙人？｣｡
They're both aliens?
｢ブー！ウワッハッハッハ｡➡
Wrong!
正解は どちらも
ムーンウォークが得意！でした｣｡
The correct answer is that both are good moonwalkers!
Altitude at 1,500 feet.
高度1500フィート｡
後輪 ガッ 前輪 ガッ 着地成功｡
Rear landing gear down.
Front landing gear down.
Landing successful.
｢グッドランディングだ！ムッタ｡
ウハハ！｣｡
Good landing, Mutta!
ただいま 減速中｡
Continuing to decelerate.
Nice flight, Max.
⦅ナイスフライトだ マックス｡
ハハハ…最高だよ！お前➡
You rule... That's a good boy.
よしよし⦆
最高だな お前｡
You rule...
Huh?
おお ムッタ｡こんな時間まで
イメージトレーニングか？
Oh, Mutta...
You're still doing image training at this hour?
ハハッ！まあな｡
今日の流れの復習だ｡
Pretty much.
I was going over today's flight again.
ヤンじいとの くだらねえ会話も
リアルに再現しつつな｡
I managed to accurately reproduce our stupid conversations.
フハハハ！そりゃいい！
Sounds fun...
なぁ ヤンじい｡ヤンじいが
いつも敬礼している所に➡
Hey, Mr. Young...
I'd noticed there are pictures on the wall you always salute.
写真があるのを発見してさ｡
今日 初めて あの写真を
ちゃんと見たんだよ｡
Today was the first day I really looked at them.
そうか…じゃあ なんとなく
わかったろ｡ムッタ➡
I see.
Then, you must understand...
彼らは みんな 事故で
じゅんしょく
殉職したパイロット達だ｡
They're all pilots who died in accidents.
彼らの ほとんどがバーディゴや
単純な操作ミスによる事故死だ｡
Most of them died due to vertigo or simple pilot error.
そして残念なことに あの中には➡
And sadly,
訓練中の事故で死んだ
宇宙飛行士が４人いる｡
four of them were
astronauts in training.
宇宙飛行士になれたのに宇宙に➡
Some of those are pictures of astronauts who never got to go to space.
行けなかった者達が
あそこに いるんだ｡
あいさつ
彼らに挨拶もなしに
アスキャンに➡
If I trained AsCans without paying my respects to them first,
操縦を教えるのは
なんか後ろめたくてな｡
I'd feel guilty...
ガム食うか？お？
Want some gum?
もらうよ｡
I'll take some.
＜この大事な事実に関して
ヤンじいは いつもの➡
Mr. Young didn't give me his usual reminder to add that piece of information to my notebook.
｢メモっとけ｣を言わなかったが➡
きっと わかってたんだろう＞
But I guess he must have known.
He didn't need to say a word,
＜言うまでもなく私の心の
しる
ノートに深く記されたと＞
since I had already put it in the notebook in my heart.
It's been so long since I looked up at the moon
Though it's always keeping a cold eye on me
Yeah, it always keeps a cold eye on me
I wanna rough up this rotten way home
But even if it makes me mad
I can't take my eyes off it. Yeah, I can't take my eyes off it
I can't take my eyes off that dazzling smile
What did I want back then?
What was I looking for?
I should've known my tears would take me to my dreams
Blow this gloomy reality away for me
I want to see how tiny our huge worries seem
From up in that dark ocean of space
Next time, on
Space Brothers
#68 Two Keyboards
Japan's first moonwalker has returned home.
＜日本人初のムーンウォーカーと
がいせん
なった日々人が凱旋帰国＞
I'll go see Sharon.
＜シャロンのとこにも顔出すよ＞
＜おう＞
Sure!
＜シャロンに 私が今できることは
何か あるだろうか…＞
Right now, is there anything I can do for Sharon?
Next time, on Space Brothers:
"Two Keyboards"
きみ
ぼく
なに
ことば
解かるよ
なんて言葉